Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you!
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem!
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see!
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonderland!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
Live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
And that's when it happened.
I looked him straight in the eye
and yelled, You bow-legged bastard!
And ever since that day,
crabs throughout the world have been
self-conscious about being bow-legged.
Oh, that's the reason
they walk sideways? Yep,
and at that pivotal moment,
a lobster happened to be within
earshot and heard the whole thing.
Oh, so lobsters are crabs too?
Better believe it. Oh.
Zoro, why don't you relax?
You're just wasting your energy
doing that who asked you excuse him.
No, he's hopeless
Guys like Zoro they got to keep
moving or they won't stay focused.
They have one-track minds especially
Our own resident muscle freak here now that
he's had a taste of the seven warlords?
Stop whining just say what's
on your mind or shut up!
Ah, you need me to spell it out?
All this tough guy bluster
is just a sad attempt
to mask your fear that
Luffy might lose this one.
Who, me?
You saying I'm scared, huh?
Is that what you're saying?
Look at me, fancy eyebrows! That's it!
I've had enough of you!
You damn Mosshead!
What'd you call me?
You wanna go at it?
Cut it out! This is pointless!
Look at them!
They're at each other's throats!
Everyone's worked up!
It's up to me as Vice-Captain to
take charge! Calm down! All of you!
Everyone's frightened, yes, but
we mustn't turn on each other!
Luffy's cowering on us
to meet him in Alubarna!
Yeah, well, you see more
on eggs than any of us!
Keep your mind on the Rebellion
and leave the rest to us!
Sorry about that, Vivi.
If we tear each other
apart, we've already lost.
All right, that's settled.
Now let's devote our
attention to Elabarna.
Full speed, scissors!
Scissors?
Name for the crab. Oh.
You just baked that up.
Got something better?
No, not really.
Water!
I can hardly believe my eyes.
Precious water!
The water is coming forth!
Didn't I tell you, Luffy?
This land is strong!
Through it all, Yuba lives on!
This sandstorm will deal Yuba
a final destructive blow.
Banning the flames of anger within the
rebel army until an inferno ignites!
But in the end, the bleeding hearts which
infest this land are what's killing it.
And you, Straw Hat Luffy,
are the worst of them all?
If only you had purged
yourself of such weakness,
you may have lived a little longer.
Water.
I assume you don't feel so
indebted to this water now.
What's this?
You're still alive?
That looks like it hurts.
But you'll be out of
your misery soon enough.
Goodbye.
That was a complete waste of my time.
Not so bad.
Once we've weathered this storm!
The rain will bless us with sweet relief.
Just like always.
Your winds will never vanquish us!
You cowardly storm?
Yuba will never give in to the sand.
Me?
Go to Alubarna?
Are we chasing after
the Straw Hat Pirates?
Or, uh, reinforcing the Royal Army?
That's up to you.
You'll have to decide which is
more important when you get there.
But, sir, I don't understand.
What's going on?
Rely on your sense of justice.
Whatever happens, I'll
accept responsibility.
Captain, where are you going?
I have to head out to sea.
Something unforeseen has come up.
Be on alert to receive
communication from me at any time.
Right.
I need you to keep a vigilant eye on
this country and where it ends up.
Whether it falls or whether it survives,
the dawn of a brand new and
historic age is on the horizon.
Sergeant Major!
Your orders! Yes.
Whether it falls or whether it survives,
the dawn of a brand new and
historic age is on the horizon.
Our target is the pirate Straw Hat
Luffy and everyone who serves under him.
All hands, reinforce your gear.
Prepare to depart for Alubarna. Right!
Straw Hat Luffy.
Damn you, Cobra.
My brethren and I are
willing to defend Alabasta
with every last drop
of blood in our bodies.
We will die before turning it over to you.
Hurry!
Step lively!
Stop dawdling around and focus!
We need more cannonballs over here!
Chaka!
The enemy's number is said
to be well over two million.
Tell me, soldier, what do you think
of His Majesty's attack on Nanohana?
I have served His Majesty for over
ten years, and I was quite surprised.
You're right.
There's really no way
anyone could rationalize it.
Logic would suggest something
has happened to the king.
If true, it is all the more reason
why we must not lose this fight.
Bury your fear deep, for your king's
sake, as well as that of Princess Phoebe.
We will defend this country at all costs.
Everyone who is not prepared to
fight, take shelter outside the city.
We cannot guarantee your safety
if you would like to stay.
If we don't get out of here,
we'll be in the line of fire.
Banks are getting hectic
down there, I see.
But it's still moving too slow!
Hurry up and fight already!
I can't see him waiting!
I can't take this!
I really don't care if
he is or isn't the king!
I've got to go out of my mind if I have
to stand here guarding him any longer!
Can't! Can't!
Can't take this!
I mean, sure,
slipping past the palace guards and
kidnapping this royal pain in the rear
is a mission which only a team of
our accomplished skills can pull off.
But now that it's over, this
assignment has become a tedious bore!
Right, Mr.
Four?
Did anything I said manage to seep
through that thick head of yours?
Slow, you're so slow!
Ugh, my back is killing me!
Chaka, Koza, you mustn't fight.
The two of you embody the
spirit of this great country.
Divided, you only weaken her resolve.
There are those who lament war.
and those who race towards it.
Just go ahead and run away. Ooh.
Still, others incite war.
But for the very few who know the truth,
they strive to prevent it.
These widely opposing viewpoints
all have one thing in common.
They are about to clash here in
the capital city of Alubarna.
What?
What do you mean we
can't cross this river?
Think about it.
Moving crabs are creatures of the desert.
They don't take to water.
Has everyone gone nuts?
It's a crab!
They can exist on land and water!
Guys, this is not good.
This is a serious problem.
Look,
if we just carelessly spend our
energy swimming across the river,
We're not gonna make it in time.
See here after the river.
There's tons of desert to deal with So if
this crab can't make
it to the other shore,
are we supposed to run the
rest of the way on foot?
We don't have a choice.
We won't make it in time.
It's absolutely impossible
Hey, I can see it Sandora
River straight ahead. Oh great.
Help us scissors pretty please I know!
Scissors loves dancer girls!
Will this do? Probably.
Whoa, I can't take it!
He's looking this way!
We're accelerating!
Bobby's won!
Great, now we've got two animals in heat!
Alright, we're moving now!
And what exactly has this
solved, Chopper? Nothing!
Go faster!
I'm seeing it, but I don't believe it.
This crab is incredible.
Way to go!
Now don't you stop, just keep on going!
Hurry, run, run, run all the way!
Go!
Keep moving!
Nothing can stop us now!
Oh, I love this crab!
Hey, what's going on?
If I didn't know better,
I think we were sinking!
You stupid crab! It's over.
No use whining about it.
Keep moving.
Hold on a second.
Are you sure there are
any boats around here?
How long will it take
us to reach the shore?
The rest of the night.
That's insane!
Thanks a lot!
Thanks for the ride!
Bye, sisters! Oh, shut up!
He's the reason we're in this mess!
What the...?
It's a Sandoran catfish!
They're rarely seen by humans!
Doesn't seem that rare to me!
Did I mention they love
to eat human flesh?
You could've told us a bit sooner!
Get off of me, dammit!
I can't see a thing with
you hanging on so tight!
Chop it!
Kong Fu to Kong Fu!
They say they were just looking
out for their fellow pupils.
Pupils? What?
They think Luffy's our master?
Please!
You really want to argue with them?
Hang in there, little guys!
Just a little further!
Thanks a lot!
Bye-bye!
Now that things are going
smoothly, can we make it in time?
I don't know.
Even riding Eyelash, I'm not
sure when we would get there.
Not to be pessimistic, but
Eyelash can only carry two of us.
If Baroque Works is gonna attack
us, it'll be from here on.
So we can't split up.
Isn't there any way for
us to stick together?
Look, over there!
What is it now?
Is it the enemy?
Don't tell me they're
here to kill us already!
No, wait! That sound!
Karoo!
I'm the Supersonic Duck Squadron!
You've come to help us, haven't you?
Karoo!
Come on!
Meat! Meat!
We may both be pirates, but you
fall grossly short on skill.
This sandstorm will deal Yuba
a final destructive blow,
banning the flames of anger within the
rebel army until an inferno ignites.
No, no, no!
Thank you.
Why do you fight?
Those of you with the name of D.
D...
Who are you people?
What are your intentions?
Apparently you don't have a
clue what I'm talking about.
I found you!
Where is Vivi?
My...
Awake already?
Now that I've studied your ability, this
won't turn out like it did last time!
Be careful, pal.
Don't want to overexert yourself.
Perfect timing.
Why don't you save the boy before he dies?
After all, if it weren't for
his courage and selflessness,
who knows if your precious princess
would have made it back alive at all.
It must please you to know Vivi's safe.
That even as we speak, she's
on her way to Alubarna,
though it's a long trip
and anything could happen.
Guess the situation is what it is.
If I'm not able to stop her, then who can?
Vivi must be protected
for everyone's sake!
Need meat!
So, the final revolt has begun.
There was a lone ship.
Hopefully that means
Princess Vivi and the others
were able to make it to
Alabasta in one piece.
I must hurry.
I pray there's still time.
Hey, kid, are you all right?
Need meat.
Meat!
Meat?
You don't need food now.
That's the least of your worries.
Hang on, I'll get a doctor for you.
I'm going to make sure
Crocodile pays for this.
He insulted Phoebe, and that old
man with this shovel gave me water.
He's definitely gonna pay!
Who is this person?
Meat.
There it is!
It's still in the distance,
but it's Alubarna!
Koza, we're less than 30 minutes away!
Yeah.
We're nearing Alubarna now!
The time has come, men!
Chaka, we've sighted the Rebel Army.
They're about 10 miles to the south.
Their forces are bearing down on
the southern gate as we speak.
East, west, south, southeast, southwest.
Guard each gate with your life.
Do not let even one of them set
foot within our walls. Right!
Hey, take a look over there.
The rebel army is approaching,
and there are so many of them.
The princess is such a little
idiot to think she can stop them.
But then, is the little idiot even coming?
Really?
Now will she show up?
Or will she not?
Or will she?
The outcome is vague.
What, what, what, what, what?
Are we sure about this?
Shouldn't we be sure?
The princess and the pirates are
really coming right at this break.
The rebel army's gonna beat them here.
I thought those idiots
wanted to stop the fighting!
Shouldn't they at least try to be on time?
I think it's entirely possible that
they won't make it soon enough.
It might even be likely, really.
After all, they did lose precious
time when they were in Rain Base.
What? They did?
All right, then.
Let's suppose the rebellion
does get started first.
What are we supposed to
do if that does happen?
We wouldn't have to do anything, would we?
Think about it.
Once the rebellion gets underway,
there's nothing even the princess
will be able to do to stop it.
All we need to do is eliminate
whoever we're told to.
Can't you even manage to figure
that much out on your own?
It sounds like you're just dying
to see some of my dance moves.
Just calm down and let it go, you two.
Ah! My back! It hurts!
Get over here and massage it, Mr.
Four!
You're coming... No!
Really?
Why didn't you tell us
that earlier, you idiot?
Ducks!
They're on ducks!
They're on ducks. Are you sure?
Do you see anything else?
Seems like their number's gone up, too!
There are six of them!
With Straw Hat out of the way, I thought
there was only supposed to be four left!
Not quite, Miss Merry Christmas.
Don't you remember what the boss said?
He told us there's that Mr.
Prince guy, too.
And apparently there's more than one
of them, so the numbers do add up.
Just do the math.
It doesn't matter.
Phoebe is our only target.
it.
What are you so worried about?
Well, Mr.
One, you say Princess Vivi
is the only one we need to
eliminate?
Okay.
Then how about you take a stab
at guessing which one she is?
They're all wearing
identical outfits!
Even worse, those birds are the
quickest in the whole kingdom.
Supersonic ducks.
You sneaky rats!
How are we supposed to tell
which one is Phoebe like this?
It's just not a fair
thing to do, you know!
Let them have it down, Mr. Four!
Dodge it!
Miss him, those damn
birds, they're too fast.
Two just broke off from the rest.
They're splitting up.
Looks like they're planning
to go for the south gate.
Those two are heading straight
toward the rebel army.
Which means one of them must be Vivi.
We'll go ahead and take care of those two.
Move it, Mr.
Four
Special attack, firestorm
Two more of them are
breaking off that way, Mr.
One!
That could be Mimi!
Seems they're planning to
go in through the West Gate.
Damn brats.
Let's go.
Okay!
Let's head for the Southwest Gate now!
So they're going to approach three of
Alibarna's five gates from the West.
If they're gonna split up and enter
that way, then we'll do the same thing.
We can wipe them out inside the city.
You're not getting away from me!
Hey, someone's coming!
Is it the Rebels?
No, wait!
It's the Supersonic Duck Squadron!
Let them in!
Oh!
I'm not kidding here!
There's no way you're
getting away with this!
Hair! Hair! Hair! Hair!
Teeheehee!
Thank you so much for
following us all the way here!
Say what?
Now stop?
Wow you guys are very good!
You know that's right!
I'm the real princess!
Bb What are you?
I mean what are you talking about?
I am the real princess!
Bb
I wonder if this is far enough now?
I have to say it's really entertaining!
How easily you all fell for this!
Now, we can go ahead and take
these silly cloaks along.
Too bad!
It looks like your guess was wrong!
Wado?!
Thank you so much, everyone.
I have to hurry now.
The rebel army is almost to the city.
Let's go, Kaido.
Camel!
And I recognize you from the
ship, too, don't I? Saru!
Yeah, come on, Zoro!
Let him have it!
Would you keep quiet over there?
They fooled us.
Quite a farce.
I don't know that anymore!
You cleared me!
It looks like there won't
be any rebellion now.
What did you say?
I have to stop them at any cost.
If I don't, then all of this
struggling has been for nothing.
Whatever the cost,
Vivi and her friends must be prevented
from making contact with the rebel army.
Secure the cannonballs!
I don't want them rolling away!
You heard him, men!
Man your posts!
Keep the artillery under control!
The ground is really moving, huh?
The enemy army is made up
of two million angry men.
Even the ground shakes
a little bit for them.
Stay strong.
It's okay, Karoo.
You don't have to be here.
You could get trampled,
so just be careful.
Please, leader, please
listen to what I have to say.
You must hear it.
Everyone listen!
Close your ranks and stay together!
We'll knock through the
guards at the southern gate!
The rest will fall from there!
Do not lose arms!
Rebel Army, you must stop!
This fight is pointless, it's all a Step!
Please slow down, you
have got to listen to me!
Rebel Army, stop!
Hey, did you see a person
standing in front of us just now?
Person?
That isn't important right now.
The enemy is already shooting at us.
Why did they do that?
Neither side can see anything now.
What is the Royal Army thinking?
What the hell?
I haven't given anyone
the order to open fire.
Do not act without my Zeus.
Uh, sir, I'm terribly sorry about that.
I guess my hand just slipped. Sorry.
Don't back down! Charge through!
It's such a cloud of sand!
No, everyone!
You have to stop now!
Fight for the country!
We'll make the king pay!
Leader!
Koza, what is it?
Nothing! It's nothing!
Was I imagining it?
Leader?
Remember a bit!
Today will be our final battle!
Wait!
Listen to me!
They're here!
Get it ready!
Fire!
Save the country!
Tare down Autobahna!
No, Karoo!
Karoo, you shielded me from them.
I'm sorry.
We've come so far.
We've done so much.
But the rebellion has started.
I'm so sorry, but I will stop it.
No matter how many times they refuse to
listen, no matter how loudly I have to yell,
we will not let mindless fighting
destroy what we've worked so hard for.
That's something I learned
while I was on board the ship.
Do not ever give up!
Phoebe!
At last, I found you!
Usopp!
We can still make it in time!
Hurry and hop on! Right.
Hang in there, Karoo.
Oh, forget about that bird.
What's the matter, Vivi?
Come on, we need to get going now.
Hurry it up!
That bird?
Let's go, Karoo!
Come on, the rebellion
will only get worse.
Usopp, prove yourself.
Hmm? Really?
You don't believe that it's me?
See?
No!
Usopp.
Hey, Usopp.
Eyelash, wake up.
Oh, it's you, Sanji.
Is it morning already?
Uh, sure.
So, this is how our fight turned out.
The part of the mission where we
lured them away went really well.
But then, well, you see, then
it was over in two seconds.
One second each.
You couldn't have held out longer?
What are you doing here anyway?
Your ducks got me.
They came to get some help for you two.
But that aside, you let Mr.
Two get away, didn't you? Yeah.
Listen up.
That creepy ballerina's
transformations are perfect.
There's no telling when he might pose as
one of us and make an
attempt on Vivi's life.
Does everyone understand?
If you ever feel like one
of us is acting suspicious,
ask them to take off this
wrapping and reveal their mark.
If they can't do that,
they're an imposter.
Whoa.
Having such a well-thought-out plan like
this seems uncharacteristically
smart for you.
So how can we be sure you
aren't already an imposter?
I'll stab you!
Yeah, that's him.
Ooh, definitely Zoro.
You're lying.
You're not really Usopp.
Well, that's too bad.
No, really.
You knew how.
I thought my imitation was perfect.
We even had a helpful
report from the boss?
That you all had the same bandages.
wrapped up on your arm like this.
So smart of you!
This isn't good.
Phoebe's in danger!